snapbuilder.com 2018-01-18

# Snap Builder Web Productions Privacy Policy

Protecting the privacy of our customers and clients is of great importance to all of us at snapbuilder.com ("Snap Builder"). This Privacy Policy explains the type of personal information we collect, and how we use, protect and disclose that information.

We are strongly committed to preserving online privacy for all of our website visitors. Our website is a general audience site, and we do not knowingly collect information about children or sell products to children. Consistent with the [Children's Online Privacy Protection Act](http://www.coppa.org/coppa.htm), we will not knowingly collect any information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, you must ask your parent or guardian to assist you in using our website.

  * __**Collection of Personal Information**. 

Affiliate/Partners use our web-based remote ordering services to allow you to place orders through the internet, mobile devices, call centers, and other "remote" methods. As a result of those orders, Snap Builder receives and collects certain personal information about our customers, which may include name, address, zip code, phone number, email address, and order history. SnapBuilder.com does not collect any credit card numbers of transactions processed. 

  * __**Location Data**. 

In some instances, our website may include various GEO location-based features, such as determining your State and Country origin. To provide these location-based features, Snap Builder and the Affiliate/Partners may collect, use and share your location data, including the real-time geographic location of your computer, tablet or mobile device. 

  * __**Use and Disclosure of Personal Information**. 

Snap Builder will not disclose your personal information to any person or entity except:   
(i) Snap Builder will send your personal and all other order information required to the Affiliate/Partners you order from using our system.   
(ii) Snap Builder may provide personal information to our authorized vendors and suppliers when necessary.   
(iii) Snap Builder may share certain personal information with our Affiliate/Partners in order to complete transactions.   
(iv) Snap Builder may transfer personal information to any successor in connection with a sale of all or substantially all of our business or assets (whether by way of stock sale, asset sale, merger, business combination, reorganization or otherwise),   
(v) Snap Builder may disclose your personal information if it is necessary in order to provide products or services to you, including purchaser verification, authentication, GEO  location and authorization for purchase order(s) and contacting the purchaser when necessary, and,   
(vi) Snap Builder may release personal information to comply with Federal or State law(s), enforce or apply the terms of any user agreement, or to protect the rights, property or safety of Snap Builder, customers and clients, and/or others. Affiliate/Partners may use your personal information to contact you concerning products, services and promotions which may be of interest to you. Upon receiving your permission, we may share your personal information with such third parties to advise you of products, services and promotions. The use of your personal information provided to such third parties is governed by their privacy policies. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of our affiliate/partners or for their collection or use of your personal information. We encourage you to read the privacy policies and statements of any Affiliate/Partners which are posted on the site from where you place your order. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Snap Builder services. Therefore, we disclaim any liability for any third party's usage of your personal information in any manner that may conflict with our privacy policy.

  * __**Safeguards**. 

The security of your personal information is very important to us. We use industry-standard technical safeguards and an employee/sub-contractor/affiliated partner code of conduct and training to help ensure the integrity and privacy of your personal information. Only authorized Snap Builder employees, agents and independent contractors are permitted to access your personal information, and all such employees, agents and independent contractors must agree to maintain the privacy and confidentiality of your personal information in accordance with our policies. 

  * __**Use of "Cookies" or Other Data Collection Tool**. 

A cookie is a piece of information which a web server may place on your computer when you visit a website. Cookies are commonly used by websites to improve the user experience and have not been known to transmit computer viruses or otherwise harm your computer. We may use cookies for a number of purposes - for example, to maintain continuity during a user session, to gather data about the usage of our website and the websites of our Affiliate/Partners for research and other purposes, to store your preferences for certain kinds of information, or to store a user name or password so that you do not have to provide this information every time you return to a website we operate. Our cookies will track only your activity relating to your online activity on our websites, and will not track any other Internet activity. You can decide if and how your computer will accept a cookie by configuring your preferences or options in your browser. If you choose to reject cookies, you may not be able to access/use certain sections of our website, online products and services. In addition to the information we collect from cookies, we may use third party analytic programs or services to track your usage of our website. 

  * __**Links to Third Party Websites**. 

For your convenience we provide links to other Affiliate/Partners websites and web pages that we do not control. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any websites or pages not under our control and we do not endorse any of these websites or pages, the services or products described or offered on such sites or pages, or any of the content contained on those sites or pages. 

  * __**Customer Service**. 

Snap Builder customer service representatives may occasionally contact you by email, with your permission, to gather information about your experiences with our Affiliate/Partners or Snap Builder services. These surveys are intended to help Snap Builder provide you with the best possible customer experience and service. 

  * __**Privacy Choices**. 

We will not send you promotional e-mails without your permission. You may choose to stop receiving surveys and/or promotional emails at any time by following the instructions contained within such emails for opting out or regulating the frequency of our emails. 

  * __**Contacting us and Deleting or Updating Personal Information**. 

You may always contact a Snap Builder representative at [our helpdesk](https://snapbuilder.com/helpdesk/) to request that we:   
(i) delete your personal information from SnapBuilder.com systems;   
(ii) update your personal information; or,   
(iii) change your preferences with respect to marketing contacts. When personal information has been provided to a Affiliate/Partners or other third party, you must also contact those entities concerning deletion or updating your personal information from their database. 

  * __**Updates to this Policy**. 

We may update this Privacy Policy at any time, and such updated Privacy Policy shall apply to your use of this website after any change has been made and posted here. The most recent version of the Policy is reflected by the version date located at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. Please check this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. 

Last updated: July, 10, 2015
